swing4ireland.com 2007-06-15

# Privacy Policy - Free irish swinging site, meet swingers today!

|   
---  

---  
**couples:**  
 **women:**  
 **men:**  

    **Total Members:** 13,655  
     **New Today:** 132  
     **Online Now:** 31   | 

**What personally identifiable information do I provide to swing4ireland.com?**

Swing4ireland.com ask you to provide various types of personally identifiable information to enhance your experience on our site. During registration, swing4ireland.com will ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, address, and other information about yourself. The more information you provide, the better we are able to customise your experience. See below about "cookies" and what other information is collected. 

Except as stated in this privacy policy or at the time of collection, a user's personally identifiable information will not be transferred to a party outside swing4ireland.com, its divisions or affiliates, or its service vendors unless notice is given at the time of collection or prior to transfer. Swing4ireland.com may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms and Conditions or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) swing4ireland.com rights or property, other swing4ireland.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**e-Commerce**

If you make a purchase of Premium Membership or any other product or service from us, your payment and purchase details will remain private and confidential, and will not be passed on to anyone else. All of our transactions are carried out on a secure server with industry-standard 128-bit SSL encryption to protect you against fraud. We do not keep your credit card details on file.

**Data Security**

We have in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to protect the information we collect online. However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet.

**What are cookies and how does swing4ireland.com use them?**

Swing4ireland.com places a "cookie" on the browser of a user's computer in order to keep you logged in to the site. This is strictly for authentication purposes only, and contains no personally identifiable information.
